Looks like someones having a bad dream?
Don't Hug Me I'm Scared 6 is a animation, horror,
music film directed by Becky Sloan.
All alone, Yellow Guy tries to stop a lamp from teaching him about dreams.
While Red Guy finds out the truth about the puppets' existence.
Yellow Guy / Duck Guy / Additional Voices (voice), played by Baker Terry.
Spinach Can / Sketchbook / Additional Voices (voice), played by Becky Sloan.
Red Guy (voice), played by Joseph Pelling.
Sammy the Spade (voice), played by Kellen Goff.
Magnet (voice), played by Thomas Ridgewell.
Lamp / Clock / Colin / Shrignold / Steak (voice)
(uncredited), played by Royngtt.
Don't Hug Me I'm Scared is a British surrealist adult puppet musical comedy horror web series created by Becky Sloan and
Joe Pelling that consists of six short episodes released on YouTube between 29 July 2011 and 19 June 2016.
It is notable for blending surrealism and dark comedy with
psychological horror and musical elements.
Its production is diverse, combining puppetry and live action with styles of animation including stop
motion, traditional animation, flash animation, claymation, and computer animation.
A sequel television series, also consisting of six episodes, was
released on All 4 and Channel 4 on 23 September 2022.
Each episode of the series starts like a typical children's programme, consisting of
anthropomorphic puppets akin to those featured in Sesame Street or The Muppets.
The series parodies and satirises these programmes by juxtaposing its inhabitants and their childlike, colourful environment against disturbing themes; each episode develops a plot twist that incorporates psychological
horror, surreal imagery, dark comedy, extreme graphic violence, and existentialism, before returning the traumatised characters to their original situation with an altered outlook as a result of their experience.
The six episodes of the web series explore creativity, time, love, technology, food, and dreams; the
television series touches on jobs, death, family, friendship, transport, and electricity.
Both have received widespread critical acclaim for their story, production design,
psychological horror, humour, hidden themes, lore, and characters.
The film explores themes of surrealism, woman director, absurdism.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.